zones.com 2014-12-03

# Privacy Policy

Zones, Inc. is committed to client privacy. We regularly review our privacy policies to ensure we remain current with legal and ethical practices, as well as ensuring the goodwill of our clients. Any subsequent updates or changes to our Privacy Policy will be disclosed here.

#### Personal Information that Zones may collect:

Zones collects personal client information such as name, address, billing information, shipping addresses, phone number, email address, and credit card and other financial information when provided to us via secure registration and order forms.

Zones may also collect personal information such as name and email address resulting from email subscriptions, surveys, requested quotes, or other registration activities when provided to us.

#### How we use that information:

Zones may use personal information to complete and satisfy orders placed and/or contact clients about their orders or registration when necessary.

Zones may also use this provided personal information to deliver promotional offers through email and postal mail and may occasionally share client names and postal addresses-not email addresses-with reputable third parties that offer products and services related to a client's interests; this activity can be cancelled at any time via the opt-out instructions near the bottom of this page.

Zones uses opt-in email registration to deliver promotional offers through email. We use provided profile information to tailor offers of potential interest to clients. This profile data is held on a secure server and is not distributed to third parties for marketing purposes.

If a client volunteers to participate in a Zones survey, the information provided will be held on a secure server. Use of this information is analyzed at an aggregate level and used to help Zones improve its business practices in order to serve clients better.

In extreme cases, where and when required by law, Zones may be forced to release client information to legal authorities in the event of credit card fraud, illegal internet use, or unauthorized use or acts committed in connection with this site.

#### Cookies and Web Logs:

Zones uses cookies, IP address and web log data to collect aggregate data about web site visitors to help us understand how to best serve clients. We may also use these methods in conjunction with a client's shopping cart and/or registration to make appropriate product, service and solution recommendations.

#### Third Party Tracking Software:

Zones may use third party tracking software to gather information about where users are coming from and how they are using our site. This data is collected and used in an aggregated form to evaluate Zones web site performance and marketing programs.

In some cases, Zones may provide contract service providers with a client's personal and transactional information in order to administer services to that specific client. Our contracts with these companies require them to maintain the confidentiality and security of all personal and transactional information and to use it only for the purpose of delivering the products or services for which they were contracted.

Zones web sites may contain links to other sites. While Zones proactively seeks to promote sound privacy polices with all its partners, we are not responsible for the privacy practices of those partners or the content of their Web sites. Zones suggests that clients review our partners' privacy policies before providing any personal information to them.

#### Affiliates and Rebate Programs:

Zones' affiliate program uses tracking links from affiliate sites to Zones sites. We use a third-party company to track and identify any purchases made through these links back to the originating site. This tracking is limited to non-identifying information and Zones does not share personal information with the affiliate partner unless our customers grant us permission to do so.

#### Security and Protection:

Zones utilizes commercially reasonable efforts to store and protect personal information against loss, illegal access, misuse, and destruction. We employ SSL-protected Web pages and 128-bit encryption technology on all pages that require personal information. This means that customer information transmitted online receives the highest degree of security currently available. Additionally, we store all client information on a secure server and limit access to this information to authorized personnel.

Zones is a Verisign certified web site. Security of Zones web sites may be checked by accessing our Verisign certificate through the Verisign image on Zones web sites' home pages. We suggest that clients use the latest version of today's most popular browsers, Microsoft Internet Explorer and Netscape Communicator, to ensure the highest level of Internet protection.

#### Opt-Out:

Zones may use client information to contact, mail, or email clients about new products and services, special promotions, exclusive offers, or upcoming events. We offer the option to opt-out of these communications at any time. Zones may also share a client's name and postal address-but not an email address-to reputable companies offering products or services that we feel may be of interest to that client. Clients that do not want us to share this information with these companies should let us know using the contact information provided below.

To be removed from a Zones marketing mailing and emailing list, clients may contact our customer service department with their first name, last name, address or email address, and zip code (for confirmation purposes only) and the client's name will be removed promptly.

**Customer Service Information:**

**Phone:** 1-800-248-9948  
**Email:** [customerservice@zones.com](mailto:customerservice@zones.com)  
**Hours:** M-F: 6 a.m. to 5 p.m. PST 

#### Children:

Zones web sites are not intended or designed for use by children under the age of 13. To comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, children under 13 should not provide us with any personal information online. We strongly urge parents to supervise their children's online activity.

#### Changes to Privacy Policy:

Zones reserves the right to amend and update its privacy policy at any time. Any updates or amendments will be posted on this page for review.

#### Access to Customer Information:

Clients have online access to their personal information with Zones at any time. Additional access to personal information is available during Zones business hours. Clients may contact Zones via the information below to review, update, or inquire about their personal information.

**How to Contact Us:**

Zones, Inc.  
1102 15th St SW, Ste 102  
Auburn, WA 98001  
**Phone:** 253-205-3000 

Or please review our complete [Contact List](http://www.zones.com/site/statics/static_page.html?name=corporate/about-us/contact-us)
